Yujian 'Charles' Tang

University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill yujian@live.unc.edu • Phone: (919) 741-4667

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My current research topic is on training neural networks to learn the segmentation of subcortical structures in macaque brains using deep learning on a convolutional neural network. Previous research experience includes image processing in neuroimaging, and data cleaning for mobile crowdsensing. Future research interests are in biomedical applications of machine learning particularly robotics and imaging.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill (Expected)

Chapel Hill, NC August 2015-May 2019

Raleigh, NC

B.S., Computer Science

Minors: Statistics, Neuroscience

PRESENTATIONS, PRECEDINGS, AND PAPERS

Reputation-Aware Data Fusion and Malicious Participant Detection in Mobile Crowdsensing (Submitted) Seattle, WA IEEE Big Data 2018, BigCyber Workshop December 10-13, 2018

Adapting the CIVET Pipeline to Rhesus Macaque Brains State of North Carolina Undergraduate Research Symposium November 10, 2018

Adapting the CIVET Pipeline for Macaque Brains Chapel Hill, NC University of North Carolina Computer Science Research Symposium May 2018

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Neuro Image Research and Analysis Labs Chapel Hill, NC Research Assistant August 2018-Present

Mentor: Dr. Martin Styner

Research Experience for Undergraduates, National Science Foundation Miami, FL Research Intern May 2018-August 2018

Mentors: Dr. Niki Pissinou, Samia Tasnim

Neuro Image Research and Analysis Labs Chapel Hill, NC Research Assistant June 2017-May 2018

Mentors: Dr. Martin Styner, and Dr. Sun-Hyung Kim

WORK EXPERIENCE

Department of Computer Science, UNC Chapel Hill, NC Undergraduate Learning Assistant (COMP 283) Fall 17, Spring 18, Fall 18

Instructor: Dr. David Plaisted

Chapel Hill, NC ITS Franklin, UNC Middleware Intern June 2017-August 2017

Department of Computer Science, UNC Chapel Hill, NC Undergraduate Learning Assistant (COMP 410) Fall 2016

Instructor: Dr. David Stotts

nCino Wilmington, NC June 2016-August 2016 Developer Intern

HONORS

NC State Math Contest Scholarship Winner, 2015 Undergraduate Learning Assistant of the Year Nominee, 2018